<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.lokalize.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਲੋਕਾਲਾਈਜ਼</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Локализуј</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Lokalizuj</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Локализуј</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Lokalizuj</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxLokalizexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Lokalize</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Lokalize</name>
  <summary>Computer-aided translation system</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ast">Sistema de traducción asistíu per ordenador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Sistema de traducció assistida per ordinador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Sistema de traducció assistida per ordinador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Systém pro překlad pomocí počítače</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Computerassisteret oversættelsessystem (CAT)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Computergestütztes Übersetzungssystem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Computer-aided translation system</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Sistema de traducción asistido por computador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Tõlkemäluga tõlkimisrakendus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Tietokoneavusteinen käännösjärjestelmä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Outil de traduction assistée par ordinateur</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Sistema de tradución asistida por computador.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Sistema di traduzione assistita</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Kompiuterizuota vertimo sistema</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Computerondersteund vertaalsysteem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Dataassistert omsetjing</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਕੰਪਿਊਟਰ-ਸਹਾਇਕ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਸਿਸਟਮ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">System tłumaczeń wspomagany komputerowo</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Sistema de traduções auxiliado por computador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Sistema de tradução auxiliado pelo computador</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Система автоматизированного перевода</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Počítačovo riadený prekladový systém</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Računalniško podprt prevajalni sistem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Систем за превођење помоћу рачунара</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Sistem za prevođenje pomoću računara</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Систем за превођење помоћу рачунара</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Sistem za prevođenje pomoću računara</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Datorstött översättningssystem</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Комп’ютерна система допомоги у перекладі</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxComputer-aided translation systemxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">计算机辅助翻译系统</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">電腦協助翻譯系統</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Lokalize is the localization tool for KDE and other open source software. It is also a general computer-aided translation system (CAT) with which you can translate OpenDocument files (*.odt). Translate-Toolkit is used internally to extract text for translation from .odt to .xliff files and to merge translation back into .odt file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Lokalize ye la ferramienta de llocalización pa KDE y otru software de códigu llibre. Ye tamién un sistema de traducción asistíu per ordenador (CAT) col que pues traducir ficheros OpenDocument (*.odt). Internamente úsase Translate-Toolkit pa estrayer el testu pa la traducción de ficheros </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Lokalize és l'eina de traducció pel KDE i altre programari de codi lliure. També és un sistema de traducció assistit per ordinador (CAT) general que amb el que es poden traduir fitxers OpenDocument (*.odt). Internament s'utilitza el Translate-Toolkit per extreure text per a la traducció des de fitxers .odt a .xliff i per tornar a fusionar la traducció al fitxer .odt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Lokalize és l'eina de traducció pel KDE i altre programari de codi lliure. També és un sistema de traducció assistit per ordinador (CAT) general que amb el que es poden traduir fitxers OpenDocument (*.odt). Internament s'utilitza el Translate-Toolkit per extreure text per a la traducció des de fitxers .odt a .xliff i per tornar a fusionar la traducció al fitxer .odt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Lokalize er oversættelsesværktøjet til KDE og anden open source software. Den er også et generet computerassisteret oversættelsessystem (CAT), hvormed du kan oversætte OpenDocument-filer (*.odt). Translate-Toolkit bruges internt til at udtrække tekst til oversættelse fra .odt til .xliff-filer og til at flette oversættelsen tilbage til .odt-filen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Lokalize ist ein Lokalisierungs-Programm für KDE und andere quelloffene Software. Es ist außerdem ein  rechnergestütztes Übersetzungssystem (CAT), mit dem Sie auch OpenDocument-Dateien (odt) übersetzen können. Intern wird „Translate-Toolkit“ zum Extrahieren von Text für die Übersetzung aus „odt“- in „xliff“-Dateien und für das Einfügen der Übersetzung zurück in „odt“-Dateien verwendet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Lokalize is the localisation tool for KDE and other open source software. It is also a general computer-aided translation system (CAT) with which you can translate OpenDocument files (*.odt). Translate-Toolkit is used internally to extract text for translation from .odt to .xliff files and to merge translation back into .odt file.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Lokalize es la herramienta de traducción para KDE y para otros proyectos de software de código abierto. También es un sistema de traducción asistido por computador (CAT) de uso general con el que puede traducir archivos OpenDocument (*.odt). «Translate-Toolkit» se usa internamente para extraer el texto para la traducción de archivos .odt en .xliff y para volver a fusionar de nuevo las traducciones en los archivos .odt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Lokalize on KDE ja muu avatud lähtekoodiga tarkvara tõlkimisrakendus. Samuti on see üldisemas tähenduses tõlkemäluga süsteem (CAT), mille abil saab tõlkida OpenDocument-faile (*.odt). Teksti eraldamiseks tõlkimise tarbeks .odt-failist .xliff-faili ja tõlke tagasiliitmiseks .odt-faili kasutatakse sisemiselt programmi Translate-Toolkit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Lokalize on lokalisointityökalu KDE:lle ja muille avoimen koodin ohjelmille. Se on myös yleiskäyttöinen tietokoneavusteinen käännösjärjestelmä (CAT), jolla voi kääntää OpenDocument-tiedostoja (*.odt). Lokalize käyttää Translate Toolkitia poimimaan käännettävän tekstin .odt-tiedostosta .xliff-tiedostoihin ja yhdistämään käännöksen takaisin .odt-tiedostoon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Lokalize est un outil de localisation pour KDE et d'autres outils open source. Il s'agit également d'un système d'aide à la traduction assisté par ordinateur pour les fichiers au format OpenDocument (*.odt). Translate-Toolkit est utilisé en interne pour extraire le texte à traduire depuis le fichier .odt vers un fichier au format .xliff puis fusionner en retour les traductions dans le fichier .odt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Lokalize é a ferramenta de localización de KDE e doutros programas libres. Tamén é un sistema xeral de tradución asistida por computador (CAT polas súas siglas en inglés) que lle permite traducir ficheiros en formato OpenDocument (.odt). Internamente usa Translate-Toolkit para extraer o texto a traducir de ficheiros «.odt» e «.xliff» e para integrar as traducións de volta no ficheiro «.odt».</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Lokalize è uno strumento di localizzazione per KDE e altri programmi a codice sorgente aperto. È, inoltre, un sistema di traduzione assistita (CAT) con il quale puoi tradurre file OpenDocument (*.odt). Translate-Toolkit è utilizzato internamente per estrarre il testo da tradurre dai file .odt a .xliff e per reinserire le traduzioni nel file .odt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Lokalize is het hulpprogramma voor lokalisatie voor KDE en andere open-source software. Het is ook een algemeen systeem "computer-aided translation (CAT)" (vertalen met behulp van de computer) waarmee u OpenDocument bestanden (*.odt)kunt vertalen. Translate-Toolkit wordt intern gebruikt om tekst te extraheren voor vertalen van .odt naar .xliff bestanden en de vertaling terug te brengen in het .odt bestand.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Lokalize jest narzędziem do tłumaczenia dla KDE i innego oprogramowania o otwartym źródle. Jest to także wszechstronny system do komputerowego wspomagania tłumaczeń (CAT), dzięki któremu można tłumaczyć pliki OpenDocument (*.odt). Zestaw narzędzi do tłumaczenia jest używany wewnętrznie do wydobywania tekstu z plików .odt do plików .xliff, tłumaczenia ich, a następnie do scalania plikami .odt na wyjściu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Lokalize é a ferramenta de traduções para o KDE e para outras aplicações de 'software' livre. Também é um sistema de traduções auxiliado por computador, com o qual poderá traduzir ficheiros em OpenDocument (*.odt). O Translate-Toolkit é usado internamente para extrair o texto a traduzir do formato .odt para ficheiros .xliff e para reunir as traduções de volta para o ficheiro .odt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Lokalize é uma ferramenta de localização para o KDE e outros softwares de código aberto. Ele é também um sistema de tradução auxiliado pelo computador (CAT), que permite-lhe traduzir arquivos OpenDocument (*.odt). O Translate-Toolkit é usado internamente para extrair texto de arquivos .odt e transformá-lo em .xliff, de forma que possam ser traduzidos e depois mesclados ao arquivo .odt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Lokalize — инструмент переводчика от KDE. Это также система автоматизированного перевода (CAT), позволяющая переводить документы OpenDocument (*.odt). Для извлечения текста из документа ODT в файл XLIFF и переноса перевода в обратную сторону используется Translate-Toolkit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Lokalize je lokalizačný nástroj pre KDE a iný slobodný softvér. Je to tiež všeobecný počítačom riadený prekladový systém (CAT), ktorým môžete prekladať súbory OpenDocument (*.odt). Prekladový toolkit sa používa interne na extrakciu textu na preklad z .odt do .xliff súborov a zlúčenie prekladov naspäť do .odt súboru.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Lokalize je prevajalno orodje za KDE in drugo odprtokodno programsko opremo. Je tudi splošen računalniško podprt prevajalni sistem (CAT), s katerim lahko prevajate dokumente OpenDocument (*.odt). Program uporablja Translate-Toolkit za razširitev besedila iz datoteke .odt v .xliff in nato uveljavitev sprememb nazaj v datoteko .odt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Локализуј је локализациона алатка за КДЕ‑ов и други отворенокодни софтвер. Такође је општи систем за превођење помоћу рачунара (ЦАТ), којим можете да преводите отворенодокументске фајлове (*.odt). Интерно се користи Преводилачки прибор за извлачење текста за превођење из *.odt и *.xliff фајлова, и за стапање превода назад у *.odt фајл.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Lokalizuj je lokalizaciona alatka za KDE‑ov i drugi otvorenokodni softver. Takođe je opšti sistem za prevođenje pomoću računara (CAT), kojim možete da prevodite otvorenodokumentske fajlove (*.odt). Interno se koristi Prevodilački pribor za izvlačenje teksta za prevođenje iz *.odt i *.xliff fajlova, i za stapanje prevoda nazad u *.odt fajl.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Локализуј је локализациона алатка за КДЕ‑ов и други отворенокодни софтвер. Такође је општи систем за превођење помоћу рачунара (ЦАТ), којим можете да преводите отворенодокументске фајлове (*.odt). Интерно се користи Преводилачки прибор за извлачење текста за превођење из *.odt и *.xliff фајлова, и за стапање превода назад у *.odt фајл.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Lokalizuj je lokalizaciona alatka za KDE‑ov i drugi otvorenokodni softver. Takođe je opšti sistem za prevođenje pomoću računara (CAT), kojim možete da prevodite otvorenodokumentske fajlove (*.odt). Interno se koristi Prevodilački pribor za izvlačenje teksta za prevođenje iz *.odt i *.xliff fajlova, i za stapanje prevoda nazad u *.odt fajl.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Lokalize är översättningsverktyget för KDE och annan programvara med öppen källkod. Det är också ett allmänt datorstött översättningssystem (CAT), som kan användas för att översätta OpenDocument-filer (*.odt). Translate-Toolkit används internt för att extrahera text för översättning från .odt- till .xliff-filer och för att infoga översättningen tillbaka i .odt-filen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Lokalize — інструмент для локалізації KDE та іншого програмного забезпечення із відкритим кодом. Це також загальна система комп’ютеризованого перекладу (CAT), за допомогою якої ви можете перекладати файли OpenDocument (*.odt). Для видобування тексту для перекладу з файлів .odt до файлів .xliff, а також для включення перекладу назад до файла .odt використовується Translate-Toolkit.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxLokalize is the localization tool for KDE and other open source software. It is also a general computer-aided translation system (CAT) with which you can translate OpenDocument files (*.odt). Translate-Toolkit is used internally to extract text for translation from .odt to .xliff files and to merge translation back into .odt file.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Lokalize 是一套為 KDE 與其它開源軟體做在地化的工具。它也是一套電腦輔助翻譯系統（Computer-Aided Translation, CAT）。您可以用這套系統翻譯 OpenDocument 檔（*.odt）。內部使用 Translate-toolkit 將文字從 .odt 檔展開為 .xliff 檔，並將翻譯合併回 .odt 檔。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://userbase.kde.org/Lokalize</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=lokalize</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdesdk/lokalize/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/lokalize.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>lokalize</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
